Guide to the Charles H. Judd, Associate Dean of the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Charles H. Judd, associate dean of the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, records
1904-1922
RU 504
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.5
The records consist of correspondence, memoranda, reports, summer school materials, course information, and subject files of Charles Hubbard Judd as associate dean of the Yale Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, professor of psychology, and dean of the Summer School of Arts and Sciences (1905-1907).
Yale University. Graduate School
Judd, Charles Hubbard, 1873-1946
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 25-B (YRG 25-B), Records of deputy, associate, and assistant deans of the Yale Graduate School.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by subject.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, memoranda, reports, summer school materials, course information, and subject files of Charles Hubbard Judd as associate dean of the Yale Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, professor of psychology, and dean of the Summer School of Arts and Sciences (1905-1907).
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Universities and colleges -- Graduate work; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Curricula; Yale University -- Graduate work; Yale University. Graduate School
- Records, 1904-1922; Accession 1934-A-002
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - General Papers
    - Correspondence of Charles H. Judd, 1906-1907 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Paper to "The Honorable Board of Education of the City of New Haven" C.H. Judd, 1907 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Special Courses for Teachers, Circa 1906-1907 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Teachers, 1919-1922 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Alumni Dinner, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Summer School Papers
    - Correspondence: November-December, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: January-July, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: September-December, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: January-February, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: March-May, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: June-October, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: November-December, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: January-February, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: March-April, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: May-June, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: July-August, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Letter Book, 1905-1906 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Letter Book, 1906 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Course Information, 1904-1905 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Catalogue Galleys, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Course Information, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Catalogue Draft, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Course Information, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 23)